<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Giveth Docs Blog</title>
        <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog</link>
        <description>Giveth Docs Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Giveth DAO: Community GIVernance]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/givethDAO</link>
            <guid>givethDAO</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Giveth has a long history of experimentation in the decentralized governance realms.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Community Project Spotlight #4]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/communitySpotlight4</link>
            <guid>communitySpotlight4</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Wow, what an exciting month it’s been since our last update. The crypto market is hitting all-time highs across the board, there’s no better time to spread the joy and make some donations to projects that are working hard to make positive changes.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Community Project Spotlight #3]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/communitySpotlight3</link>
            <guid>communitySpotlight3</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[It’s time for another batch of great projects from Giveth.io, hand-picked by our contributors. We have six amazing projects to feature in this edition of the community spotlight.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Community Project Spotlight #2]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/communitySpotlight2</link>
            <guid>communitySpotlight2</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We’re back with another fresh batch of amazing projects on Giveth.io. We have six projects from a wide range of causes that we are featuring in this project spotlight. This is also an extra special spotlight because Giveth.io itself is currently active and accepting donations on the latest round of Gitcoin Grants (GR11). If you feel inspired by the Giveth mission after reading this article then consider making a contribution via our Grants listing and learn about the magic of Quadratic Funding! More on that later…]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Community Project Spotlight #1]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/communitySpotlight1</link>
            <guid>communitySpotlight1</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We’re back with a silver platter of community curated projects to celebrate and highlight! Our Giveth contributors went through the list and chose their top picks. We’ve found six great projects that are live on Giveth now and looking for funding to meet their goals. Read on to discover some of our favourite projects from a diverse range of causes using our DApps.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Giveth TRACE is Live 🚀]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/traceLaunch</link>
            <guid>traceLaunch</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the official full release of_** Giveth TRACE **_— a platform for traceable, accountable, effective donations powered by blockchain technology.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Change-Makers: Final Round-up!]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/changeMakersFinal</link>
            <guid>changeMakersFinal</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Giveth has been buzzing with action! While we’ve been hard at work behind-the-scenes building for our community, Giveth change-makers have been hard at work creating positive impact on the ground. We are excited to share with you one final round-up of projects in the Change-Maker Campaign.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Change-Maker Submissions — Round Up #2!]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/changeMakersRoundup2</link>
            <guid>changeMakersRoundup2</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We asked our community to add their projects to giveth.io and share their stories about how they are changing the world for the better using #giveth4change. Keep reading for our second round of submissions, or submit your story via twitter or reddit to be featured in our next round up.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What DAppened: April 21— May 5]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/whatDappened3</link>
            <guid>whatDappened3</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Upholding our values of Transparency and Accountability by sharing recent development updates from this past sprint.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The First Change-Maker Submission Roundup is In!]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/changeMakersRoundup1</link>
            <guid>changeMakersRoundup1</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We asked our community to add their projects to giveth.io and share their stories about how they are changing the world for the better using #giveth4change. Read on to discover our first round of submissions, or submit your story via twitter or reddit to be featured in our next summary.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What DAppened: March 31 — April 14]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/whatDappened2</link>
            <guid>whatDappened2</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We’re back with another development update from our recent sprint cycle! Read on to stay in-the-know on what’s dAppening at giveth.io]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Calling All Change-Makers!]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/changeMakers</link>
            <guid>changeMakers</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Are you passionate about changing the world for the better? We want to hear how you’re taking action to improve upon a social or environmental issue that speaks to you. Tell us how you’re making a difference. Share your story.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What DAppened: March 17–31]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/whatDappened1</link>
            <guid>whatDappened1</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hello friends and fans of Giveth! This is one part of a series of short transparency posts where we keep you in the loop with updates on what’s in development for giveth.io.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Two Flavors of Giveth.. Which One to Choose?]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/flavorsOfGiveth</link>
            <guid>flavorsOfGiveth</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Giveth TRACE and Giveth.io landing pages]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Giving is Here]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/futureofGiving</link>
            <guid>futureofGiving</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We are very excited to announce the launch of Giveth at giveth.io — a free, open-source donation application for community philanthropy featuring an all-new UI/UX.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to contribute to documentation]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/howToDocs</link>
            <guid>howToDocs</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hello dear contributor!]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Giving is Realigning Incentives]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/realigningIncentives</link>
            <guid>realigningIncentives</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A Trade leaves things as they were, with no external Surplus. A Gift creates a Surplus as it spreads. ~ Seth Godin]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Unicorn DAC, a Non-hierarchical Decentralized Governance Experiment]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/unicornDACexperiment</link>
            <guid>unicornDACexperiment</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Why are bosses necessary? They aren’t. Self-managed organizations exist all over the world, but there is no template for how a decentralized self-managed organization should work. Let us try to change that.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Work: Distributed Teams & Decentralized Workspaces]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/futureOfWork</link>
            <guid>futureOfWork</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The world is changing at a rapid pace. Gone are the days where you could work 30 years at a company, then get a fancy watch and a golden handshake into retirement. The industrial revolution of the early 1800’s brought more people out of the country and into factories and workshops, attracted by better pay.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Giveth Masterpiece Manifesto]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/masterpieceManifesto</link>
            <guid>masterpieceManifesto</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We asked you (our community) to dig deep into your hearts and minds, to give us your best version of the Giveth Manifesto. The results did not disappoint.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Decentralized Giving could have helped (and will help) increase Transparency and avoid Cases like Oxfam’s Scandal]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/decentralizedGiving</link>
            <guid>decentralizedGiving</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Oxfam, consistently rated one of the best NGOs in the world and a household name in most western countries, is mired in a scandal over allegedly abusing of both people and funds in Haiti during the aid mission deployed after the hurricane Harvey. Not only this, but it is also accused of its employees exchanging aid for sexual favours, plain and simple sexual abuse. The case has opened the door for a cry of the nonprofit sector to uncover and denounce these practises, which seem to be more common than one would think.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Liquid Democracy…What That?!?]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/liquidDemocracy</link>
            <guid>liquidDemocracy</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Welcome to the future of voting.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is the Future of Giving?]]></title>
            <link>https://docs.giveth.io/blog/futureOfGiving2017</link>
            <guid>futureOfGiving2017</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Edit: for the current status of the development, more recent updates here]]></description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>